greenville.k12.sc.us 2003-12-03

# SDGC Privacy Policy

Tuesday, December 02, 2003 |    
---|---  
  
 Download Print Version  

##  Web Site Privacy

Greenville Schools Online is maintained by The School District of Greenville County. The District is committed to ensuring the privacy of all our web site users. This document explains our collection and use of personal information.

### Collection of Personal Information

Greenville Schools Online does not collect personal information about individuals without their knowledge. Personal information may be requested when you engage in any of the following online activities:

  * Register on our site to use services available only to registered users;

  * Use District Email;

  * Submit information for content or editorial purposes, such as news items, letters of opinion, press releases;

  * Submit information to the site via a form. This includes activities such as completing a user survey or online application.

### Use of Personal Information

Personal information submitted **will not** be transferred to any non-affiliated third parties unless otherwise stated at the time of collection.

##### When you submit information with our on line forms:

When a user submits personally identifiable information it is used only for the purpose stated at the time of collection. For example, our On Line Job Application is stored to provide you and our Human Resources Department access to the account. No information collected is shared with any other party.

When you use a form on Greenville Schools Online, we may request your email address as a unique identifier. If you provide your email address, you may choose to receive the following:

  * Announcements of service enhancements

  * Information about new web site features

  * Surveys designed to collect information.

If you do not wish to receive these emails, select that option at the time of registration.

Personal information submitted for content or editorial purposes may be used both on the web site and in publications of The School District of Greenville County.

##### Information submitted with on line "Email" feature: 

When a registered user of email at greenville.k12.sc.us obtains an account, personally identifiable information is stored to provide individual access to the account. No information collected is shared with any other party or used for any purpose other that to insure the privacy of your account.

### Anonymous data

While personal information is protected, we sometimes collect anonymous data about your computer's capabilities and/or your online browsing pattern. This information is used to improve the design of our web site.

##### Cookies

Greenville Schools Online may place a small text file, called a "cookie", in the browser files of your computer. The cookie enables us to track your use of our web site to determine which areas you use most frequently. It enables us to see what portions of the site interest you most, but this is anonymous in nature. That is, it does not contain any personal information about you. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you choose to not accept cookies, you will not be able to use certain features we offer to registered users. If you choose to be a registered user, you must accept a cookie from us.

### Kids and Parents

Portions of our site are intended for use by children. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas or forums. Minors under the age of 18 are prohibited from registering on our sites. If you have questions or concerns about your child's online activities and/or privacy on our web site, contact the District at 241-3100.

### Log files

The District uses Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. IP addresses are used to gather broad demographic information, such as a visitor's country, operating system, browser types, frequency of visit, and so on.

### Security

The Greenville County Schools takes reasonable precautions to protect your personal information. When you submit information via the web site, it is protected both online and off-line. When personal information is required, that information is stored in a secure file on our server. This information is not accessible from the web.

We also take precautions to protect user information off-line. All user information is restricted to authorized employees. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task, for example, a Human Resources Job Specialist, are granted access to personal information. The server used to store personal information is kept in a secure environment.

### Contact Information

If you have comments, questions, or concerns about our privacy policy, or want to be removed from our database, please contact us in one of the following ways:

  * Send email to [webmaster@greenville.k12.sc.us](mailto:webmaster@greenville.k12.sc.us)
  * Send postal mail to the following address: 
    * 301 Camperdown Way  
P.O. Box 2848  
Greenville, South Carolina  
29602
  * Call our INFOLine service at the following telephone number: 864-241-3100.

Updated on May 23, 2002

 Download Print Version
